{
  "cities": [{
      "id": "1",
      "question": "What is the capital of Germany?",
      "answer": "Berlin",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "What is the capital of France?",
      "answer": "Paris",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": "Which city has the oldest still operating university in the world?",
      "answer": "Bologna",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "Which city is called The Silicon Valley Of Europe ?",
      "answer": "Berlin",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "In which city is the European Court of Human Rights located?",
      "answer": "Strasbourg",
      "difficulty": 2
    }
  ],
  "pirates": [{
      "id": "6",
      "question": "To which pirate belonged the two hundred ton, forty-gun frigate named the Queen Anne's Revenge.",
      "answer": "Blackbeard",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "question": "Which pirate liked to use fire and smoke effects in combat to scare his enemies?",
      "answer": "blackbeard",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "question": "Who was the only pirate captain to resist when Woodes Rogers asserted governorship over Nassau in 1718?",
      "answer": "Charlesvane",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "question": "Which pirate did not actually exist?",
      "answer": "Jacksparrow",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "10",
      "question": "Which former pirate became a pirate hunter himself?",
      "answer": "Benjamin hornigold",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "11",
      "question": "Which pirate is the inspiration for a commonly known brand of rum?",
      "answer": "Henry Morgan",
      "difficulty": 1
    }
  ],
  "animals": [{
      "id": "12",
      "question": "Which animal carries its heart in its head?",
      "answer": "Shrimp",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "13",
      "question": "Which animal sleeps up to three years at a stretch?",
      "answer": "Snail",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "14",
      "question": "Which is the only animal that cant jump?",
      "answer": "Elephant",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "15",
      "question": "Which mammal is not able to fart?",
      "answer": "Kangaroo",
      "difficulty": 2
    }
  ]
}